<root><source><id /><name /></source><channelid><videos><video><title>Trump's annual financial disclosure released to public</title><description>The documents show a 2017 payment to attorney Michael Cohen for between $100K-$250K; chief White House correspondent John Roberts reports.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T18:40:47.000Z</timestamp><id>bYYCXlM3eUU</id></video><video><title>New worship center to be built in Sutherland Springs</title><description>Parishioners will head to new building after shooting</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T18:36:31.000Z</timestamp><id>urOPg-mjf0o</id></video><video><title>Senate Intel Committee says Russia favored Trump in 2016</title><description>Committee leaders break with House Republicans' conclusion in the ongoing Russia Investigation; Peter Doocy reports from Capitol Hill.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T18:08:09.000Z</timestamp><id>AnJ-3H7854o</id></video><video><title>Prince Harry&#8217;s strained relationship with tabloids</title><description>Days before the royal wedding, Prince Harry and Meghan Markle&#8217;s private affairs are once again fodder for tabloids across the world. Harry has had a tumultuous relationship with the press since his childhood.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T17:36:13.000Z</timestamp><id>9jsverek03A</id></video><video><title>Man dies after vape pen explodes</title><description>A Florida was killed when his vape pen exploded, sending projectiles into his head and causing a small fire in his house. His official cause of death was listed as "projectile wound of the head" and ruled accidental.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T17:35:53.000Z</timestamp><id>Yo96HEEuB3w</id></video><video><title>New drama just days before royal wedding</title><description>Meghan Markle's family becomes tabloid fodder; Jonathan Hunt reports from Los Angeles.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T17:35:30.000Z</timestamp><id>6YVx6iIXHxc</id></video><video><title>Celebs weigh in on Yanny vs. Laurel debate</title><description>Take a listen to the audio clip that&#8217;s dividing the internet and find out what celebrities are saying. Do you hear &#8216;Laurel&#8217; or &#8216;Yanny&#8217;?</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T16:36:36.000Z</timestamp><id>tsK679nKCq0</id></video><video><title>Fears grow of Kilauea eruption as plumes reach 12,000 feet</title><description>Hawaii issues aviation red alert as volcano spews plume of ash; Jeff Paul reports from that National Guard Base in Hilo, Hawaii.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T16:06:19.000Z</timestamp><id>gqeJtd7Hbh4</id></video><video><title>Don Jr. 'never discussed' Trump Tower meeting with Trump</title><description>Releases from Senator Chuck Grassley includes the closed-door testimony of Donald Trump Jr. and others who met with Russian lawyer; Ellison Barber reports from Washington.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T15:36:51.000Z</timestamp><id>zPHmgNIB9tE</id></video><video><title>Trump Tower meeting documents released</title><description>Documents: Donald Trump Jr. was skeptical about the Trump Tower meeting. Washington Examiner's Tom Rogan on what to look for in the documents.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T13:54:27.000Z</timestamp><id>u7S6fYXlnR8</id></video><video><title>Sanders: Trump is ready if North Korea meeting takes place</title><description>On 'Fox &amp; Friends,' White House press secretary on North Korea threatening to cancel the U.S. summit and the Haspel confirmation process. Also, Sanders slams leaking as 'disgusting and shameful behavior.'</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T13:37:23.000Z</timestamp><id>Cbq_jMUUHuw</id></video><video><title>Anti-NRA, anti-GOP signs at school covered, but still up</title><description>Philadelphia school's signs that take aim at the GOP and NRA are sparking outrage. Outraged parent says the kids are being used as pawns.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T12:36:50.000Z</timestamp><id>LJ3RpWGu_JM</id></video><video><title>Jimmy Kimmel uses nun to joke about Met Gala</title><description>Wall Street Journal columnist, William McGurn, says Sister Pat's life is about self-sacrifice.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T12:36:49.000Z</timestamp><id>dmugT1ehEpI</id></video><video><title>Dershowitz: Media incentivize Hamas with biased reporting</title><description>Israel defends itself from Hamas invasion. Harvard Law professor opens up about his meeting with Israeli Prime Minister Netanyahu.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T12:36:20.000Z</timestamp><id>R79zZtH_LB0</id></video><video><title>Trump-bashing causing the blue wave to crash?</title><description>Should Democrats change their midterm strategy? Strategists Ned Ryun and Richard Goodstein debate on 'Fox &amp; Friends First.'</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T11:36:41.000Z</timestamp><id>UkF2QWMtwxM</id></video><video><title>North Korea threatens to cancel summit with President Trump</title><description>U.S., South Korea military drills could end summit. Heritage Foundation senior fellow James Carafano weighs in on 'Fox &amp; Friends First.'</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T11:35:52.000Z</timestamp><id>7zoSsQFhJhw</id></video><video><title>Hume: Democrats' message 'indistinct'</title><description>Fox News senior political analyst Brit Hume: Democratic party is obsessed with Trump and the anti-Trump message, but it's not working out well for them in the polls. #Tucker</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T09:36:10.000Z</timestamp><id>0hS-dU13Mx0</id></video><video><title>Minnesota daycare fraud scheme has possible link to terror</title><description>What appears to be rampant fraud in a state program is costing taxpayers as much as $100 million a year and could be going overseas to fund terrorism; State Sen. Jim Abeler reacts on 'Fox News@ Night.'</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T04:37:43.000Z</timestamp><id>QeP2KoV68_k</id></video><video><title>GOP chairmen want info on Comey friend Daniel Richman</title><description>Republican Congressman Andy Biggs, who sits on the House Judiciary Committee, joins 'Fox News @ Night' to discuss the DOJ's response.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T04:36:44.000Z</timestamp><id>PO2UrBncUKU</id></video><video><title>Rep. Barletta to face Democratic Sen. Casey in Pennsylvania</title><description>The four-term congressman and staunch supporter of President Trump wins the Republican nomination for U.S. Senate; Eric Shawn reports.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T04:36:08.000Z</timestamp><id>3pekdlfFTtQ</id></video><video><title>Secretary Nielsen talks immigration, relationship with Trump</title><description>Homeland Security Secretary Kirstjen Nielsen joins 'The Ingraham Angle' to discuss her relationship with President Trump and the administration's plan to end catch-and-release on the border.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T03:37:22.000Z</timestamp><id>ywDalba3jB4</id></video><video><title>Ingraham: DACA detour jeopardizes GOP's new midterm momentum</title><description>Leave it to a liberal band of Republicans to splinter the party, just when unity is needed most.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T03:36:22.000Z</timestamp><id>QlOX5mJ8bN8</id></video><video><title>Goodlatte responds to Republican revolt on immigration</title><description>Centrist Republicans aim to force DACA debate in the House with discharge petition; GOP Congressman Bob Goodlatte weighs in on 'The Ingraham Angle.'</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T03:36:21.000Z</timestamp><id>vLig8TknKaM</id></video><video><title>What Trump can learn from Reagan's negotiations with USSR</title><description>Bret Baier, anchor of 'Special Report' and author of 'Three Days in Moscow,' joins 'Hannity' to discuss similarities between President Trump and Reagan's foreign policy strategies.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T02:38:26.000Z</timestamp><id>WiFXFIU8zYc</id></video><video><title>Media take shots at Trump, Ivanka over Mideast violence</title><description>New York Daily News equates Ivanka Trump to a demon; reaction on 'Hannity' from Dan Bongino, NRATV contributor and former Secret Service agent, and The Hill's Joe Concha.</description><timestamp timezone="UTC">2018-05-16T02:37:37.000Z</timestamp><id>nn5XtvWDwaM</id></video></videos></channelid></root>